Are you getting paranoid?
You're paranoid, huh?
No. I just don't think
you're gonna like it up there.
Where, Helen?
I've been there before.
Fourth grade. Field trip.
Tamika Rich threw up.
No, the festivities, Fastnacht.
It's really traditional.
Oh. Well,
if we don't like it, we can
just go back to the lodge,
and do lodge stuff.
"Lodge stuff"?
Yeah, lodge stuff.
I know it sounds gross,
but it's pretty much what
we were doing this morning.
And you'll be high, so you'll
have more tongue confidence.
You notice that?
Now I'm paranoid.
This is gonna sound like a
high question, but it's not.
Got it.
Are black women considered brunettes?
Is it weird that made me hungry?
You, too?
Oh, shit.
This is nice.
We're gonna be the only
black people here, aren't we?
Christina's half.
The important thing
is the Faschingstanz,
and make sure you mix in
some actual dance moves
with the traditional
ones. They'll love that.
- All right.
- We're gonna win for sure.
Christina's gonna be so mad,
'cause Dave can't dance for shit.
I'm not that great, either.
I don't know. You got some swag.
It's weird swag, but people like it.
Oh, by the way, traditionally,
there's a moor character
that people show up in blackface, so...
- Great.
- Mm-hmm.
When you were a kid,
didn't you feel, like,
weird about all that?
Hmm, I used to.
But I'm kind of like the Serena
Williams of the festivities.
They hate, but they
can't deny the stats.
You're so competitive.
I know. And you love it.
Hey, baby.
Hey!
- Oh, my God. Hi.
- It is so good to see you.
- What's up, Van? How are you?
- Hey, Dave.
I'm good. Ha, look.
- Hey, yo!
- Amazing.
- That looks good.
- Love it.
- Look at you.
- Look, I told you she'd dress up.
Earn.
Earn!
You want to take our picture?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, um...
- Huh.
There we go.
- I took three.
- Thank you.
Where is your costume?
Oh, yeah. That's not me.
I'm not really into...
Y-Yeah, but you got to dress up, man.
I mean, like, why are you here?
- Look at me. I'm wearing lederhosen, dawg.
- Yeah.
I-I get it. I don't know.
Van likes it.
- Where-where'd she go, though?
- Yo.
- I got a spare mask in the whip.
- I'm...
- I'm all right, man.
- You sure?
- I'm sure, man.
- You'd look good in it.
I feel good like this.
What the hell is that?
It's a Schnappviecher.
It's a demon thief.
Every Fastnacht, he steals something
from one unlucky villager.
No way!
You look so good!
Oh.
You look great... and I'm sorry.
Where's that mask you
were talking about?
Yeah, it's in the whip.
Cool.
Welcome to another Fastnacht.
Here, take these, please.
- Game on.
- Thank you.
We've got some excellent prizes tonight,
provided by Dixie Gas.
Big shout-out to Dixie Gas
for these two movie gift cards.
And I don't know about the rest of you,
but I'm ready to Hootz-Kutz.
Just bounce the ball
to me when it comes,
but don't say "Hootz-Kutz"
unless you have to. Okay.
- He's never played.
- Okay, okay.
Are we ready to Hootz-Kutz?
Yeah!
On-on my count. Ready,
set, go.
- Oh!
- Come on, Earn.
You're supposed to catch it, okay?
- I'm sorry. All right, sorry.
- It's okay.
Go.
There it is!
We're supposed to pass them.
- Don't just...
- Oh, my God!
Switch!
Hold, hold.
Thank you.
Earn, you're just standing there, dude.
Earn.
- Earn, don't just stand there.
- Earn.
What'd you... whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Whoa. That was crazy.
How'd you do that?
I just put the...
I just held the balls
and put them in the jug.
Shh, no, no. No, hold on.
I've been playing Hootz-Kutz
since I was a little kid, and I've...
I've never seen anyone do that.
Shit, dude.
No, seriously, man.
How-how did you do that?
I just held the balls
and-and put them in the jug.
Oh, my goodness.
Earnest "Halten" Marks!
Give it up for Earn!
Earn! Earn!
Earn! Earn! Earn! Earn! Earn!
What's "halten"?
It just means "to hold."
You really should learn German.
Yeah, I know. It's so useful.
You got lucky as fuck back there.
You should listen to me next time.
You're starting to sound more
like Serena Williams's dad.
Hello.
What can I get you?
- Wow.
- Uh...
No.
Okay.
Did you understand that?
No.
Okay.
The mask, maybe...?
Mm... yeah.
Ding, ding. How about some service?
Wow.
Here you go.
There's always gonna be more girls, man.
I get that, but...
But how are you supposed
to know what you want
the rest of your life right now?
Sometimes I feel like
she wants me to be lame.
I mean, like, this
isn't me. I mean, like...
You know, I don't know, maybe she wants
a guy who could speak German.
You know what I'm say...
A guy who enjoys dancing to polka music.
I'm not that dude.
I-I don't know why she wants me
to pretend like I'm that dude.
Well, she just, you know, wants
to spend more time with you,
and that's what girls
do when they like you.
They just want to twist
their life up with yours.
That way, it's harder to disconnect.
- Hey.
Um, so, the guys are
dancing in three minutes.
You want to go over some moves?
Yeah, actually, let's
go over here for a sec.
Okay.
Ping-Pong.
No. This is obviously a
traditional Pingen-Pong...
- tablisch...
- Tischtennisplatte.
- Yeah, that's what I said.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I was just thinking
we could spend some
one-on-one time together.
Can we spend some
one-on-one time dancing?
It's just one game.
Come on. It's the
only white game I know.
Okay. But one game.
If I win,
no more complaining.
We dance
and my name is on the
front of the trophy.
- Fair.
- Okay.
- And if I win...
- Mm...
- Come on.
- Oh.
- Mm, mm. Mm-hmm.
- Okay, well,
don't be upset when you're
in a weird sexual position.
You need a warm-up? Come on.
Let's go. Best out of three.
Ready?
- Okay.
- Ready?
Baby, I thought you used to play.
Yeah, okay.
Come on.
Come on, Serena. Let's
do it. You got it.
Fuck.
That's two out of three, baby.
Mm-hmm. Come on.
Let's go dancing. It's match point.
Why'd you do that?
What're you talking
about? This was your idea.
Yeah, but when we play basketball,
I don't just destroy you
in front of everybody.
There's nobody here.
They're all dancing.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry. Was he here the whole time?
He was standing right next to me?
Let's go. Come on. You lost. Let's go.
I'm-I'm not in the mood.
Seriously?
You're being a fucking baby.
Fine. I'll do it if I fucking have to.
This is typical.
- Whatever.
- Wait. Hold up. I'm sorry. What?
I said I'll do it if we fucking have to.
You don't have to do shit.
We do your shit all the fucking time.
We went to a strip club.
- You liked the strip club.
- I liked going to a strip club?
I'm a woman. I need to go
fucking look at titties?
- Then just say you don't enjoy it.
- No.
- You didn't like that.
- I want to just spend time with you.
- It doesn't matter to me.
- Well, I was trying
- to fucking spend time with you.
- I wanted to go dancing.
It's fucking stupid.
I don't like it.
But you can't do it for me?
I'm not trying to go to
fucking Alfred's concerts
every fucking weekend.
I wouldn't shit on that.
That's paying your fucking bills.
Wow.
Yeah.
You can be real mean, man.
Fuck you.
♪ One: don't pick up the phone,
you know he's only calling ♪
♪ 'Cause he's drunk and alone ♪
Where'd Earn go?
Ugh. He's being a baby.
I don't understand what...
he wants from me.
- Christina. Oh, my God.
- Oh! Hi.
- How are you, Flo?
- It's so good to see you. So good!
- I'm so glad you're here.
- What's going on?
Oh, just everything.
- Yeah?
- I know. It's so good to see you.
- It's so good to see you, too.
- Did you see Jen here?
I vaguely remember. I think I saw her.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh! Oh.
This is Flo. Flo, this is Lottie's mom.
Oh, my God.
So nice to finally meet you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Kai is in love with Lottie.
She's just so polite and
sweet when she's at our house.
Oh. She better be.
Uh, hi. I'm Tek.
- It's nice to meet you.
- You, too.
Babe, this is Lottie's mom.
- Right. Okay, Earn's girl.
- Yes.
- Right. Yeah, I've heard a lot about you.
You know, Earn's making
some really cool moves
with Paper Boi. People
are really impressed.
- Thank you.
- So...
Tek hears all the tea at the label.
Yeah, a lot of tea.
I handle his publishing.
So, do you work with Earn,
or you an artist?
No, I'm sort of in
between things right now.
I stay at home mostly.
Oh, she used to be a teacher.
- Oh, that's great.
- Yeah.
You're so lucky.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Babe. What's going on?
- Wait. W-W-Wait.
- I just need a drink.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Let-Let's sit down.
Let's sit... No, no, no, seriously.
Come. Sit down.
It's gonna be fine.
What's going on?
I don't know why you
have to introduce me
as Lottie's mom.
- You know my first name.
- Yeah, but...
And that's not all that I'm gonna be
for the rest of my
life, is Lottie's mom.
Of course not. I know that.
But you make that shit look good.
Like, it's different for you.
What do you... what do you mean?
You know, it just seems like something
that you're more ready for.
- What do you mean?
- Because...
you know, like, you chose Earn.
I chose Dave.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, like, since we were kids.
Like, I chose white.
You chose black. Like, it's...
Okay.
- No.
- You... Yeah.
I didn't choose black.
Yes, you did.
You never hung out with me and Melanie
when we invited you.
And you only went to the black parties.
I mean...
it's like you needed that identity.
Yeah, but you...
But Melanie was never nice to me.
Well, I mean,
you never invited me to your parties.
That's because, um,
you always acted like
you were better than us,
and you would pander to us
and say shit like, "I
wish I had kinky hair."
Which you do. You
just... you straighten it.
So it's, like, weird
to... it's weird to say.
- Do you know what I mean?
- I didn't, and I think
- you're going way too far.
- What?
- Like, seriously?
- You literally just told me
that I'm gonna be a baby mama,
and that's okay because I "chose black."
Well, of course...
- Are you serious?
- Babe!
We won, babe!
- Will you take a pic? My phone's died.
- Yeah.
Yay.
Shit. I don't know where my phone is.
I thought I had it.
- I just had it.
- For real? Really?
- Yeah.
- Did someone get Schnapped?
It is now the witching hour.
Who here has been struck
- by the Schnappviecher?
- Right here!
Right here!
Wudeljagd!
Wudeljagd, Wudeljagd!
Wudeljagd, Wudeljagd, Wudeljagd!
_
Okay.
Hello?
Hi.
_
You find it?
Uh-huh.
Vanessa Keifer is this year's warrior!
You want a rematch?
What do you want?
A rematch.
I mean in our relationship.
This feels like a trap.
It's not a trap.
No bullshit. What do you want?
You want me to go first?
Please.
I want to be...
in a committed relationship
where I'm valued as a human being
and not as an accessory
that you can fuck.
That's a good answer.
Um...
I don't know what I want. I...
I know this... arrangement works for me.
So it works for you.
So, you don't want to change anything?
This definitely feels like a trap.
I don't want to keep
having this conversation.
I'm really tired.
Well, we don't have to
have this conversation now.
We can talk about it in the morning.
Well, I don't want to keep
waiting around for you.
And I don't want you to
waste any more of your time.
Then let's settle it.
If I win,
you only have to see me if
it's about Lottie or money.
That's not what I meant.
Then beat me.
I don't see what this is gonna prove.
It's gonna prove that I'm tired.
All right.
Best of five.
Sorry.
Um, I'll pick up Lottie
from my mom's house.
Tomorrow.
All right. Bye.